Contact

SenseQue Technologies Pvt Ltd. A-708, Titanium Square, Thaltej Cross Roads, Sarkhej - Gandhinagar Hwy, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380054, India +91 9909896575 (Mobile) yuvraj.parmar@senseque.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yuvrajparmar-18487216 (LinkedIn) senseque.com (Company)

Top Skills

ASP.NET

Web Services

C#

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Full Professional)
Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Microsoft Specialist

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer: Web Applications

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer: App Builder Charter

Member

Microsoft Certified Professional

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate: Web Applications Charter Member

Yuvraj Parmar

Director (Microsoft Technologies) at SenseQue Technologies Pvt Ltd Old Ahmedabad

Summary

A graduate in Master of Computer Application with 14+ years of experience in the field of Information Technology with exposure to diverse businesses as well as technology domains (involving IT Infrastructure Management, Television Automation / Transmission, Solution Architecture, and Project Implementation & Management, Offshore Software Development Center Delivery / Operations).

As a head of Microsoft Technologies in SenseQue Technologies today, I am responsible for delivering various IT solutions to Enterprise & Consumer markets. As part of the role, I provide innovative vision, strategy & leadership in all areas of technology use, planning, development, and support for different solutions.

Management Activities:

- · Planning and Defining Scope
- Activity Planning and Sequencing
- Resource Planning
- Developing Schedules, Time Estimating, Cost Estimating & Developing a Budget
- · Creating Charts and Schedules
- Risk Analysis
- Managing Risks and Issues
- Monitoring and Reporting Progress
- Team Leadership
- Strategic Influencing
- Business Partnering
- Scalability, Interoperability and Portability Analysis
- Controlling Quality

Specialties:

IT Outsourcing Company, Offshore Software Development, Custom Application Development, Application Maintenance & Testing, Multimedia, Rich Internet Applications, Mobile Application Development, Digital Marketing, Cloud-based Application.

We customize business models for client's flexibility considering the Requirement & Industry. We strictly mean to make your business easy and less time consuming using the latest technology.

DM me your requirements here or at yuvraj.parmar@senseque.com and I will give in depth technology consulting relevant to your business.

Experience

SenseQue Technologies
1 year 5 months
Director (Microsoft Technologies)
June 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

Director Of Operations April 2019 - June 2019 (3 months) Ahmedabad Area, India

Netpair Infotech CEO July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Ahmedabad Area, India

TechBlocks
Tech Lead
April 2014 - April 2017 (3 years 1 month)
Ahmedabad Area, India

Gateway TechnoLabs Pvt. Ltd. (Gateway Group of Companies) Analyst Programmer June 2010 - May 2014 (4 years)

Global Tech India Pvt Ltd Sr. Software Developer January 2007 - June 2010 (3 years 6 months)

Tata Consultancy Services Retainer June 2006 - May 2007 (1 year) Gandhinagar

Priya Softweb Solutions Pvt. Ltd. Sotware Developer April 2005 - May 2006 (1 year 2 months) Ahmedabad Area, India

Education

AITS RAjkot

Master of Computer Applications (MCA), Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2003 - 2005)

GLS Institute, Ahmedabad

BCA, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology · (2001 - 2003)